{
    "id": "93ace158305f4837a9136e758513758e",
    "title": "Comparatives And Superlatives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is .......................  older than him.",
            "description": "We can use much to modify comparatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "more",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a29b6d757ab44e4ebe0e879de1895eab"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ........................... brilliant student in the class.",
            "description": "We use the before the superlatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "mostest",
                "more",
                "the most"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "83034cffbde946b9a243ff923265364b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The journey is as important ............................... the destination.",
            "description": "To say that two things are equal or similar, we use the construction as....as...",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0636244e174d4c36bc3c60df29f17e65"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ............................... successful than me.",
            "description": "More successful is the comparative term. We can use much to modify comparatives.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "much more",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1a9484639cc94230be012314ad9a092b"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is more expensive ............................. I thought.",
            "description": "Than is the conjunction used in comparative structures.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ba53556bbceb4ac0bbbe94e8592ae6f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ................................. woman I have ever seen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "most beautiful",
                "the most beautiful",
                "the beautifullest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "55ced0425eb8481f814af1e9ff5bc1ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't walk any .............................",
            "description": "Both further and farther can be used to talk about distance.",
            "answers": [
                "farther",
                "further",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c0ee979b2b624c34ac583c8919c9726b"
        },
        {
            "question": "This fabric is inferior ................................. that fabric.",
            "description": "After superior and inferior, we use 'to' not 'than'.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e2ad08cbd9de4068a937b59a524fdd3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the ............................. of the two sisters?",
            "description": "When a group has just two people, we use the comparative instead of the superlative.",
            "answers": [
                "pretty",
                "prettier",
                "prettiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef96a24772a147c8a92b6b02c34beeb1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your accent is ............................. than mine.",
            "description": "Worse is the comparative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "worse",
                "worser",
                "worst"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7899fd2f81b8400fb3cd512508c576e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The car is running .............................. since it had a service.",
            "description": "More smoothly is the comparative form of smoothly. ",
            "answers": [
                "more smoothly",
                "smoothlier",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ad5b0c1a88ef493faa3537af4287b0c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She earns …………………………. than I do.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative form of little.",
            "answers": [
                "less money",
                "little money",
                "lesser money"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee5b34c174ef4fe1a0fdec5554fc336f"
        }
    ]
}